A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Journal of General Physiology, Editorial Correspondence, Series 2 FA925
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Editorial Correspondence, 2
  - GP #3844: Knauf, Philip A., Proverbio, Fulgencio, and Hoffman, Joseph F. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - GP #3845: Dennison and Bozof (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - GP #3846: Needleman, Douglas, Johnson and Jakschik (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - GP #3847: Brown and Brown (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - GP #3848: Gordon, Godt, Donaldson and Harris (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - GP #3849: Eguchi, Waterman and Akiyama (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - GP #3850: Parker (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - GP #3851: Brenner and Rathmayer (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - GP #3852: Williams, John A. and Matthews, E.K. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - GP #3853: Williams, John A. and Matthews, E.K. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - GP #3854: Dowling and Ripps (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - GP #3855: Hillman et. Al. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - GP #3856: Bozler and Delahayes (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - GP #3857: Chapman (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - GP #3858: Van Bruggen, Boyett and Van Beuren (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - GP #3859: Harosi and Macnichol (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - GP #3860: Dipolo (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - GP #3861: Russell and Blaustein (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - GP #3862: Detwiler and Alkon (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - GP #3863: Wright, Brown and Wald (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - GP #3864: Schaeffer, John F., Preston, Robert L. and Curran, Peter F. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - GP #3865: Lockshin (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - GP #3866: Langer, Serena, and Nudd (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - GP #3867: Applewhite, Satter and Galston (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - GP #3868: Orentlicher, Reuben, Grandfest and Brandt (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - GP #3869: Somlyo, Smiesko and Somlyo (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - GP #3870: den Hertog and Jager (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - GP #3871: den Hertog and Jager (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - GP #3872: den Hertog and Jager (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - GP #3873: Jackson and Shiau (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - GP #3874: Jackson, Shiau, Bane and Fox (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - GP #3875: Toyoda, Jun-ichi (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - GP #3876: Blatt, F.J. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - GP #3877: Silver (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - GP #3878: Shiraishi (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - GP #3879: Miyamoto and Kasai (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - GP #3880: Naccache and Sha?afi (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - GP #3881: Jesaitis (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - GP #3882: Lannergren and Noth (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - GP #3883: Ruegg (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - GP #3884: Ruegg (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - GP #3885: Pollack and Huntsman (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - GP #3886: Parsons, Schnitzler and Cochrane (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - GP #3887: Scarpa and Graziotti (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - GP #3888: Cividalli and Nathan (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - GP #3889: McCann (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - GP #3890: Spenney, Shoemaker and Sachs (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - GP #3891: Ferguson and Schuttz (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - GP #3892: Chertok and Lake (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - GP #3893: Blank and Mozell (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - GP #3894: Heller and Van der Kloot (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - GP #3895: Dunn (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - GP #3896: Pinto and Pak (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - GP #3897: Pinto and Pak (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - GP #3898: Tarr and Trank (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - GP #3899: Tarr and Trank (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - GP #3900: Sandborn (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - GP #3901: Brown and Mote (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - GP #3902: Malcolm (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - GP #3903: Eunice Bloomquist and Brian A. Curtis (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - GP #3904: Elford and Solomon (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - GP #3905: Nakajima and Bastian (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - GP #3906: Bastian and Nakajima (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - GP #3907: Valdiosera, Clausen and Eisenberg (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - GP #3908: Valdiosera, Clausen and Eisenberg (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - GP #3909: Valdiosera, Clausen and Eisenberg (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - GP #3910: Nakamura and Yasumasu (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - GP #3911: Yasumasu and Nakamura (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - GP #3912: Beall, Tosteson et.al. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - GP #3913: W.R. Galey and Jeffrey D. Owen (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - GP #3914: Thames, Teichholz and Podolsky (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - GP #3915: J.E. Harris and M. Morad (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - GP #3916: Kregenow (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - GP #3917: Kidokoro, Grinnell and Eaton (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - GP #3918: Lehman, Bullard and Hammond (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - GP #3919: Mehaffey and Berson (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - GP #3920: Owen, Steggall and Eyring (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - GP #3921: Chesnais, Corabouef, Sauviat and Vassas (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - GP #3922: Macon (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - GP #3923: Hagiwara, Fukuda and Eaton (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - GP #3924: Palmer and Gulati (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - GP #3925: Shporer and Civan (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - GP #3926: Barlow and Lange (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - GP #3927: Axelrod and Klein (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - GP #3928: Winegrad (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - GP #3929: Olson and Cazort (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - GP #3930: Danisi and Vieira (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - GP #3931: Pak and Lidington (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - GP #3932: Getchell (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - GP #3933: Wladimiroff, Craft and Talbert (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - GP #3934: Van der Kloot et.al. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - GP #3935: Wu and Pak (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - GP #3936: Schafer, Patlak and Andreoli (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - GP #3937: Schafer, Troutman and Andreoli (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - GP #3938: Srebro and Behbehani (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - GP #3939: Srebro and Behbehani (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - GP #3940: DiPolo and Caputo (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - GP #3941: Greenwald and Kirschner (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - GP #3942: Kirschner and Sanders (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - GP #3943: Kiremidjian and Stotzky (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - GP #3944: Desjeux, Tai and Curran (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - GP #3945: Chambaut, Leray, Pecker et.al. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - GP #3946: Ahearn (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - GP #3947: Silverman (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - GP #3948: Alkon (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - GP #3949: Ehrenstein, Blumenthal, Latorre and Lecar (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - GP #3950: Lange and Gary Bobo (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - GP #3951: Kriebel and Gross (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - GP #3952: Offner and Kim (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - GP #3953: Schiff (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - GP #3954: S.M. Pemrick and C. Edwards (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - GP #3955: Thompson and Ballew (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - GP #3956: Miyamoto and Breckenridge (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - GP #3957: Brutsaert and Claes (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - GP #3958: Schoenberg, Wells, Podolsky (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - GP #3959: Swanson and Solomon (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - GP #3960: Mobley, Leung and Eisenberg (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - GP #3961: Ewald Komor, Widmar Tanner (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - GP #3962: Connor, Barr and Jacobson (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - GP #3963: Alkon (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - GP #3964: Issei Seyama and Toshio Narahashi (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - GP #3965: Schafer, Troutman and Andreoli (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - GP #3966: Kustin, Ladd and McLeod (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - GP #3967: Kleinzeller et.al. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - GP #3968: Sato and Beidler (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - GP #3969: Costantin (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - GP #3970: Begenisich and Lynch (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - GP #3971: Reuss and Finn (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - GP #3972: R.L. Satter, G.T. Geballe, P.B. Applewhite and A.W. Galston (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - GP #3973: Satter, Geballe et.al. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - GP #3974: Armstrong and Bezanilla (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - GP #3975: Donaldson and Kerrick (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - GP #3976: Sidney Cohen (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - GP #3977: Weissberg and Katz (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - GP #3978: Winegrad (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - GP #3979: Tsien (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - GP #3980: Tsien (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - GP #3981: Rothstein (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - GP #3982: Chappell and Devoe (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - GP #3983: Tashiro and Nishi (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - GP #3984: Goldstein, Freygang and Gunn (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - GP #3985: Illinois, Joyner et.al. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - GP #3986: Julian and Sollins (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - GP #3987: Kustin et.al. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - GP #3988: Lieberman and Lundegard (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - GP #3989: Preston, Schaeffer and Curran (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - GP #3990: Mullins and Brinley (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - GP #3991: Gerolf Gros and Waldemar Moll assisted by Heike Hoppe and Hanne Gros (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - GP #3992: Bonner and Carlson (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - GP #3993: Fambrough (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - GP #3994: Homsher, Rall et.al. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - GP #3995: Nosek, Kornacker, etc. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - GP #3996: Wiggins and Cranefield (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - GP #3997: Landowne (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - GP #3998: Spiegler and Yeandle (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - GP #3999: Brown and Blinks (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - GP #4000: Eaton, Russell and Brown (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - GP #4001: Anagnostopoulos (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - GP #4002: Peter Shrager (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - GP #4003: Sorbi and Cavaggioni (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - GP #4004: Al-Awoati, Beauwens (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - GP #4005: DiPolo (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - GP #4006: Murphy, Herlihy et.al. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - GP #4007: Pour-Hassani (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - GP #4008: Bozler (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - GP #4009: Rothstein et.al. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - GP #4010: O'Mahony (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - GP #4011: Redwood, Rall and Perl (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - GP #4012: Woods and Lieberman (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - GP #4013: Jacques (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - GP #4014: Beauge (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - GP #4015: Rosemary Thompson (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - GP #4016: Thompson (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - GP #4017: Rotshenker and Palti (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - GP #4018: Walton, DeLorenzo, Curran and Greengard (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - GP #4019: Giacobino and Girardier (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - GP #4020: Chinet and L. Girardier (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - GP #4021: Seydoux, Brauser and Girardier (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - GP #4022: O'Connell (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - GP #4023: Lee and Fozzard (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - GP #4024: Witkovsky, Dudek etc. (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - GP #4025: Parker, John C. et.al. (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - GP #4026: Villegas, et.al. (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - GP #4027: Ruiz-Ceretti etc. (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - GP #4028: Easton and Moore (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - GP #4029: De Haan and Harry A. Fozzard (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - GP #4030: Anninos and Cyrulnik (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - GP #4031: Gibbons and Fozzard (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - GP #4032: Gibbons and Fozzard (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - GP #4033: Carpenter et.al. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - GP #4034: Schwartz et.al. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - GP #4035: Eisenstadt, Schwartz (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - GP #4036: Eisenstadt and Schwartz (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - GP #4037: W. Otto Friesen (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - GP #4038: W. Otto Friesen (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - GP #4039: W. Otto Friesen (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - GP #4040: Sperling and Hubbard (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - GP #4041: Mobley, Leung et.al. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - GP #4042: Hillman and Hochstein et.al. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - GP #4043: Ueda, Kobatake et.al. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - GP #4044: Alvarez, Latorre etc. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - GP #4045: Alkon (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - GP #4046: Schoenberg, et.al. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - GP #4047: Steffin (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - GP #4048: Hartline and Maynard (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - GP #4049: Motokawa and Satir (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - GP #4050: Nakajima, Bastian et.al. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - GP #4051: Green, Dowling et.al. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - GP #4052: Goldman (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - GP #4053: Wesley and Wohltmann (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - GP #4054: Wholtmann and Wesley (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - GP #4055: White and Lord (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - GP #4056: Finn (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - GP #4057: Barlow and Quarles (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - GP #4058: Lieberman et.al. (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - GP #4059: Alain Marty and Alan Finkelstein (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - GP #4060: Mandel (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - GP #4061: Castranova and Miles (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - GP #4062: Castranova and Miles (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - GP #4063: Hanahi and Hillman (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - GP #4064: Villegas et.al. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - GP #4065: Gund, Tosteson et.al. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - GP #4066: Matsumoto and Mori (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - GP #4067: R.S.Sjodin and Ortiz, Olga (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - GP #4068: Hagiwara, Ozawa et.al. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - GP #4069: Moreno (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - GP #4070: Moreno (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - GP #4071: Kinne, Murer, Sachs et.al. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - GP #4072: Mason, Bresler etc. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - GP #4073: Branisteanu and Wolfe (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - GP #4074: Parisi, Gauna et.al. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - GP #4075: Spring and Giebisch (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - GP #4076: Spring and Giebisch (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - GP #4077: Zeidler and Lee (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - GP #4078: Lum and Henkin (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - GP #4079: Lum, Henkin and Whittaker (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - GP #4080: Banks (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - GP #4081: B.Bromm (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - GP #4082: Miyake, Kamo et.al. (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - GP #4083: Hargraves and Mandelkern (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - GP #4084: Spenne, Flemstrom etc. (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - GP #4085: Geduldig and Livengood (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - GP #4086: Fischkoff and Vanderkooi (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - GP #4087: Taraskevich (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - GP #4088: Branisteanu, etc. (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - GP #4089: Henderson and Cattell (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - GP #4090: Ritchie and Fambrough (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - GP #4091: Chaplain, Frommelt (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - GP #4092: Harza and Matyas (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - GP #4093: Hiraoka and Fozzard (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - GP #4094: Frizzell, Dugas et.al. (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - GP #4095: Paolini and Roos (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - GP #4096: Pumplin and McClure (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - GP #4097: Owen and Eyring (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - GP #4098: Van Netten and Belton (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - GP #4099: Smith and Wagner (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - GP #4100: Ihler, Lantzy et.al. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - GP #4101: Larmie and Webb (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - GP #4102: Lester, Changeux et.al. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - GP #4103: Johnston and Wachtel (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - GP #4103 rev.: Johnston and Wachtel (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - GP #4104: Johnston and Wachtel (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - GP #4105: Feinstein and Fraser (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - GP #4106: Kass and Tsien (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - GP #4107: Mobley and Eisenberg (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - GP #4108: Morel and LeBlanc (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - GP #4109: LeBlanc and Morel (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - GP #4110: Goldinger and Omachi (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - GP #4111: Julian and Sollins (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - GP #4112: Begenisich (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - GP #4113: Goldman, Barnes, etc. (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - GP #4114: Ueda, Kurihara, etc. (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - GP #4115: Nathan, Pooler and De Haan (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - GP #4116: Kaplan and Barlow (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - GP #4117: Ferenc I. Harosi (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - GP #4118: Watson, Olivelle etc. (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - GP #4119: Oxford and Pooler (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - GP #4120: Nunes and Vieira (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - GP #4121: Cohen, Jan, Matricon and Delbruck (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - GP #4122: Cohn and Tanner (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - GP #4123: Cohn and Green (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - GP #4124: Ritchie and Fambrough (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - GP #4125: Schafer, Patlak (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - GP #4126: Howell and Huff (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - GP #4127: Brunker (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - GP #4128: Lisman and Brown (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - GP #4129: Lisman and Brown (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - GP #4130: Katz and Lindheimer (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - GP #4131: Devoe (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - GP #4132: Lehman and Szent-Gyorgyi (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - GP #4133: Caswell, Baerwald, etc. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - GP #4134: Sato, Ogawa et.al. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - GP #4135: Bownds and Brodie (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - GP #4136: Guy de Renzis (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - GP #4137: Machemer and Eckert (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - GP #4138: Alkon (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - GP #4139: Proske and Rack (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - GP #4140: Kang and Lee (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - GP #4141: Kang and Lee (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - GP #4142: Borle and Uchikawa (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - GP #4143: Lee and Cha (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - GP #4144: Brinley et.al. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - GP #4145: Gallagher, Tashiro etc. (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - GP #4146: Jackson, Michael J. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - GP #4147: Kleinhaus (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - GP #4148: K.S. Cole (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - GP #4149: Carpenter, Hovey etc. (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - GP #4150: Kleinschmidt and Dowling (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - GP #4151: Rose, Nahrwold etc. (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - GP #4152: Dasgupta and Dubey (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - GP #4153: Sachs (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - GP #4154: Neville, Nordstrom (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - GP #4155: Boron and De Weer (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - GP #4156: Spring and Giebisch (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - GP #4157: Borejdo and Oplatka (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - GP #4158: Miller and Dacheux (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - GP #4159: Miller and Dacheux (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - GP #4160: Miller and Dacheux (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - GP #4158-4160 rev.: Miller and Dacheux (Papers I-III) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - GP #4160: Miller and Dacheux (Papers I-III) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - GP #4161: Suszkin, Beach etc. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - GP #4162: Sreter, Luff and Gergely (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - GP #4163: Bertil Hille (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - GP #4164: Gilai (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - GP #4165: Gilai (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - GP #4164 (rev.)/4165 (rev.): Gilai (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - GP #4166: Barker and Levitan (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - GP #4167: Bodemann and Hoffman (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - GP #4168: Bodemann and Hoffman (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - GP #4169: Belmonte and Stensaas (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - GP #4170: Mommaerts, Vegh etc. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - GP #4171: Hodson and Wei (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - GP #4172: Manalis and Gilbert (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - GP #4173: Ohtsu (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - GP #4174: Fein and Charlton (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - GP #4175: Hato, Ueda, Kurihara and Kobatake (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - GP #4176: Adams (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - GP #4177: Rutherford (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - GP #4178: Mahlon E. Kriebel (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - GP #4179: Sacklin and Boulpaep (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - GP #4180: Schauf and Davis (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - GP #4181: Elder, Morre and Yunghans (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - GP #4182: Ahearn (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - GP #4183: Owen, Steggall etc. (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - GP #4184: Saji (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - GP #4185: Hastings and Gutknecht (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - GP #4186: Janis, Crankshaw (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - GP #4187: Crankshaw, Janis etc. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - GP #4188: Dalmark (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - GP #4189: Akaike (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - GP #4190: Akaike and Kiyohara (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - GP #4191: Alkon (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - GP #4192: Bodemann and Hoffman (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - GP #4193: Brazy and Gunn (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - GP #4194: Poznansky, Tong etc. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - GP #4195: Kupferman and Weiss (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - GP #4196: Al-Awoati et.al. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - GP #4197: Hall (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - GP #4198: Barnola and Villegas (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - GP #4199: Schauf and Davis (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - GP #4200: Browning and Nelson (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - GP #4201: Browning and Nelson (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - GP #4202: Citttadini and van Rossum (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - GP #4203: Brown, Brodwick, etc. (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - GP #4204: Baur, Brown et.al. (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - GP #4205: Brown and Tuley (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - GP #4206: Kawai and Brandt (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - GP #4207: Paul and Kushmerick (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - GP #4208: Briggs, Rothstein etc. (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - GP #4209: Hille and Campbell (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - GP #4210: Campbell (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - GP #4211: Campbell and Hille (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - GP #4212: Schneider and Chandler (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - GP #4213: Chandler and Schneider (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - GP #4214: David Rhoads, Fred B. Waters and Wolfgang Epstein (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - GP #4215: Macdonald, Keizer etc. (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - GP #4216: Macdonald and Jobsis (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - GP #4217: Robblee and Shepro (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - GP #4218: Daley and Vande Berg (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - GP #4219: Zamir (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - GP #4220: Kirchberger and Tada (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - GP #4221: Brown and Pinto (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - GP #4222: Villefas, Sevcik etc. (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - GP #4223: Margolis (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - GP #4224: Gilbert and Matsumoto (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - GP #4225: Jennings and Solomon (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - GP #4226: Zeidler and Willis (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - GP #4227: Zeidler and Willis (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - GP #4228: Graves and Gutknecht (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - GP #4229: Graves and Gutknecht (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - GP #4230: Terayama, Ueda et.al. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - GP #4231: Daniel L. Alkon (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - GP #4232: Bader, Baumann etc. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - GP #4233: Arch and Smock (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - GP #4234: Orentlicher, Brandt and Reuben (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - GP #4235: Jaimovich, et.al. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - GP #4236: Fitts and Holloszy (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - GP #4237: Wood and Harvey (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - GP #4238: George W. Ordal (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - GP #4239: Lewis, Smith and Kim (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - GP #4240: Satow and Kung (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - GP #4241 Smith and Halt (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - GP #4242: Smith and Halt (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - GP #4243: Smith and Halt (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - GP #4244: McCall (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - GP #4245: Adolph (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - GP #4246: Morad and Goldman (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - GP #4247: Mazziotti, Farnsworth (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - GP #4248: Kashiwagura et.al. (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - GP #4249: Chow, Crandall etc. (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - GP #4250: Hartline and Lange (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - GP #4251: Anderson, Hirsch etc. (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - GP #4252: Rall, Homsher etc. (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - GP #4253: Starzak, Senft etc. (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - GP #4254: Meussner and McKinley (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - GP #4255: Hunter, Fayad etc. (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - GP #4256: Bell, Bradbury etc. (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - GP #4257: Best, Kerrick etc. (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - GP #4258: DiPolo, Requena etc. (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - GP #4259: Kass and Tsien (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - GP #4260: Strumwasser and Wilson (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - GP #4261: Lisman and Sheline (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - GP #4262: Winegrad (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - GP #4263: Heyer, Muller etc. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - GP #4264: Heyer, Muller etc. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - GP #4265: Hara and Hara (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - GP #4266: Haugen and Sten-Knudsen (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - GP #4267: Solomon, Kirkwood etc. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - GP #4268: Hooper and Dick (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - GP #4269: Hagiwara et.al. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - GP #4270: Mathias, Clausen etc. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - GP #4271: Sato, Sato et.al. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - GP #4272: Hsieh and Johnson (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - GP #4273: Robinson and Johnson (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - GP #4274: Dusenbery (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - GP #4275: Sevcik (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - GP #4276: Lim and Fischbag (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - GP #4277: Hartt and Johnson (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - GP #4278: Schultz and Frizzell (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - GP #4279: Koh (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - GP #4280: Koh (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - GP #4281: Gous, Lindner et.al. (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - GP #4282: Nellans and Schultz (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - GP #4283: McLean, Renaud etc. (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - GP #4284: Weingarten and MacDonald (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - GP #4285: Gros, Moll, Hoppe etc. (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - GP #4286: Gedney and Ostroy (Box 52, Folder 27)